https://manlysurfschool.com/privacy

Web Privacy Policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
(1)       What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a)       information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;
(b)       information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;
(c)        information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;
(d)       information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;
(e)       any other information that you choose to send to us; and
(f)        OTHER INFORMATION
(2)       Cookies
We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes.  We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you. Our advertisers may also send you cookies.
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website.  Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
(3)       Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a)       administer the website;
(b)       improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
(c)        enable your use of the services available on the website;
(d)       send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
(e)       send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(f)        send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(g)       send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(h)       send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications (relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by emailing us)
(i)         provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
(j)         deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and
(k)        other uses
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
(4)       Other disclosures
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:
(a)       to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)       in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)        in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
[(d)      to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5)       International data transfers
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
If you are in Australia, information which you provide may be transferred to countries including the United States, Japan, and other countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in Australia. You expressly agree to such transfers.
(6)       Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.
(7)       Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
(8)       Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee.
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)
(9)       Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(10)     Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(11)     Contact
The full name of our company is Sydney Surf School Pty Ltd trading as Manly Surf School and our address is:
P.O Box 160
Collaroy  NSW  2097.
Our ABN number is 43 062 717 891.
